A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, Accession 2013:091 FA1220
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, Accession 2013:091
1999-2012
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund.
FA1220
17.1 Cubic Feet 45 letter-size document boxes.
Arrangement
The files are arranged in the order in which they were received from the Commonwealth Fund.
Biographical / Historical
The Commonwealth Fund was founded in 1918 by Mrs. Stephen (Anna) Harkness with the mandate that it should "do something for the welfare of mankind." Most of the Fund's grants throughout its existence have been in the broad field of health. Over the years, The Commonwealth Fund's work led to the development of the field of child guidance, contributed to the emergence of progressive public health departments in communities throughout the country, supported the construction of rural hospitals, and funded the development of new medical schools in the United States. Several facets of the Fund's continued interest in health are seen in this collection, including the Fund's concern for the "underserved" or vulnerable populations in the United States, including children, minority populations, and the financially disadvantaged.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The material in this collection was received from The Commonwealth Fund in 2013.
Scope and Contents
The material in this collection documents The Commonwealth Fund's grant-making from the early 2000s through to the early 2010s. The grant files typically include the official paperwork including correspondence, proposal developments, and grant products.
Health care policy -- United States
- Project HOPE / Wilensky, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  General
  #20050157
- Project HOPE / Wilensky - Proposal Development, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Project HOPE / Wilensky - Grant Products, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- National Academy of Social Insurance / King, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  #20031356
- National Academy of Social Insurance / King - Proposal Development, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Social Insurance / King - Grant Products, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 6-8, Box 2, Folder 9)
- Trustees of Columbia University / Knitzer, 2005-2010 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  #20060364
- Trustees of Columbia University / Knitzer - Proposal, 2005-2010 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Trustees of Columbia University / Knitzer - Grant Products, 2005-2010 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Trustees of Columbia University / Knitzer - Correspondence, 2005-2010 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- University of Utah / Norlin, 2008-2011 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  #20080342
- University of Utah / Norlin - Proposal, 2008-2011 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- University of Utah / Norlin - Grant Products, 2008-2011 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- University of Utah / Norlin - Correspondence, 2008-2011 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle, 2007-2009 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  #20070768
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle - Proposal, 2007-2009 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle - Grant Products, 2007-2009 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle - Correspondence, 2007-2009 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Academic Pediatric Association / Minkovitz, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  #20070764
- Academic Pediatric Association / Minkovitz - Proposal, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Academic Pediatric Association / Minkovitz - Grant Products, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Academic Pediatric Association / Minkovitz - Correspondence, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- George Washington University / Rosenbaum, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  #20080334
- George Washington University / Rosenbaum - Proposal, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- George Washington University / Rosenbaum - Grant Products, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- George Washington University / Rosenbaum - Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- National Conference of State Legislatures / King, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  #20070736
- National Conference of State Legislatures / King - Proposal, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- National Conference of State Legislatures / King - Grant Products, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- National Conference of State Legislatures / King - Correspondence, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Children's Hospital of Philadelphia / Forrest, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  #20060375
- Children's Hospital of Philadelphia / Forrest - Proposal, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Children's Hospital of Philadelphia / Forrest - Grant Products, 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Park Nicollet Institute / Fowles, 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  #20060455
- Park Nicollet Institute / Fowles - Proposal, 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Park Nicollet Institute / Fowles - Grant Products, 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Guilford Child Health / Earls, 2005-2007 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  #20060397
- Guilford Child Health / Earls - Proposal, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Guilford Child Health / Earls - Grant Products, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 43-45)
- Yale University / Cleary, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  #20060114
- Yale University / Cleary - Proposal Development, 2005-2008 (Box 7, Folder 47-48)
- Yale University / Cleary - Grant Products, 2005-2008 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Arizona State University - University of Rochester / Melnyk, 2004-2008 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  #20040634
- Arizona State University - University of Rochester / Melnyk - Proposal Development, 2004-2008 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Arizona State University - University of Rochester / Melnyk - Grant Products, 2004-2008 (Box 7, Folder 52, Box 8, Folder 53)
- Mathematica Policy Research / Ireys, 2005-2007 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  #20060134
- Mathematica Policy Research / Ireys - Proposal Development, 2005-2007 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Mathematica Policy Research / Ireys - Grant Products, 2005-2007 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Boston Medical Center Corporation / Sege, 2006-2008 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  #20070063
- Boston Medical Center Corporation / Sege - Proposal, 2006-2008 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Boston Medical Center Corporation / Sege - Grant Products, 2006-2008 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Center for Health Policy Development / Gauthier, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  #20090641
- Center for Health Policy Development / Gauthier - Proposal, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Center for Health Policy Development / Gauthier - Grant Products, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Kaiser Foundation Health Plan of Colorado / Beck, 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  #20080150
- Kaiser Foundation Health Plan of Colorado / Beck - Proposal, 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Kaiser Foundation Health Plan of Colorado / Beck - Grant Products, 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- University of Chicago / Heckman, 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  #20070716
- University of Chicago / Heckman - Proposal, 2007-2010 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- University of Chicago / Heckman - Grant Products, 2007-2010 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Connecticut Children's Medical Center / Dworkin, 2007-2010 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  #20080118
- Connecticut Children's Medical Center / Dworkin - Proposal, 2007-2010 (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Connecticut Children's Medical Center / Dworkin - Grant Products, 2007-2010 (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Tufts Medical Center / Perrin, 2008-2011 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  #20090084
- Tufts Medical Center / Perrin - Proposal, 2008-2011 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- Tufts Medical Center / Perrin - Grant Products, 2008-2011 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle, 2008-2010 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  #20090086
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle, 2008-2010 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle - Grant Products, 2008-2010 (Box 11, Folder 77)
- Center for Health Policy Development / Kaye, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  #20100308
- Center for Health Policy Development / Kaye - Proposal, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 79)
- Center for Health Policy Development / Kaye - Grant Products, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Academy Health / Martinez-Vidal, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  $20090378
- Academy Health / Martinez-Vidal - Proposal, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  #20090378
- Academy Health / Martinez-Vidal - Grant Products, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 83)
- National Governors Association Center for Best Practices / Nolan, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  #20100047
- National Governors Association Center for Best Practices / Nolan - Proposal, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 85)
- National Governors Association Center for Best Practices / Nolan - Grant Products, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 86)
- American Academy of Pediatrics / Wilson, 2004-2010 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  #20040151
- American Academy of Pediatrics / Wilson - Proposal, 2004-2010 (Box 13, Folder 88)
- American Academy of Pediatrics / Wilson - Grant Products, 2004-2010 (Box 13, Folder 89)
- Health Management Associates / Silow-Carroll, 2008-2010 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  #20080335
- Health Management Associates / Silow-Carroll - Proposal, 2008-2010 (Box 13, Folder 91)
- Health Management Associates / Silow-Carroll - Grant Products, 2008-2010 (Box 13, Folder 92)
- University of Vermont / Shaw, 2006-2010 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  #20070065
- University of Vermont / Shaw - Proposal, 2006-2010 (Box 14, Folder 94)
- University of Vermont / Shaw - Grant Products, 2006-2010 (Box 14, Folder 95)
- Case Western Reserve University / Drotar, 2005-2007 (Box 14, Folder 96)
  #20060127
- Case Western Reserve University / Drotar - Proposal Development, 2005-2007 (Box 14, Folder 97)
- Case Western Reserve University / Drotar - Grant Products, 2005-2007 (Box 14, Folder 98)
- Pennsylvania Health Law Project / Bacharach, 2007-2010 (Box 14, Folder 99)
  #20070676
- Pennsylvania Health Law Project / Bacharach - Proposal, 2007-2010 (Box 14, Folder 100)
- Pennsylvania Health Law Project / Bacharach - Grant Products, 2007-2010 (Box 15, Folder 101)
- Boston Medical Center Corporation / Sege, 2008-2010 (Box 15, Folder 102)
  #20080147
- Boston Medical Center Corporation / Sege - Proposal, 2008-2010 (Box 15, Folder 103)
- Boston Medical Center Corporation / Sege - Grant Products, 2008-2010 (Box 15, Folder 104)
- American Academy of Pediatrics / Paul, 2006-2009 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  #20060128
- American Academy of Pediatrics / Paul - Proposal Development, 2006-2009 (Box 15, Folder 106)
- American Academy of Pediatrics / Paul - Grant Products, 2006-2009 (Box 16, Folder 107)
- Oregon Health and Science University / Bethell, 2006-2009 (Box 16, Folder 108)
  #20060568
- Oregon Health and Science University / Bethell - Grant Products, 2006-2009 (Box 16, Folder 109)
- University of Vermont and State Agricultural College / Shaw, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 110)
  #20090085
- University of Vermont and State Agricultural College / Shaw - Proposal, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 111)
- University of Vermont and State Agricultural College / Shaw - Grant Products, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 112)
- Health Management Associates / Silow-Carroll, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 113)
  #20090345
- Health Management Associates / Silow-Carroll - Proposal, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 114)
- Health Management Associates / Silow-Carroll - Grant Products, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 115)
- Stanford University / Bergman, 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  #20070072
- Stanford University / Bergman - Proposal, 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 117)
- Stanford University / Bergman - Grant Products, 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 118)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 119)
  #20090608
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle - Proposal, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 120)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle - Grant Products, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 121)
- SHIRE / Perot, 2003-2006 (Box 17, Folder 122)
  #20030678
- SHIRE / Perot - Proposal, 2003-2006 (Box 17, Folder 123)
- SHIRE / Perot - Articles and Background, 2003-2006 (Box 17, Folder 124)
- SHIRE / Perot - Grant Products, 2003-2006 (Box 18, Folder 125-127)
- University of California, Irvine / Mukamel, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 128)
  #20010555
- University of Rochester / Mukamel, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 129)
- University of Rochester / Mukamel, 2001-2006 (Box 19, Folder 130-131)
- Medicare Rights Center / Hayes, 2003-2006 (Box 19, Folder 132)
  #20030374
- Center on Budget and Policy Issues / Ku, 2003-2006 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  20030375
- National Academy of Social Insurance / Larson, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  #20060638
- University of Pennsylvania / Sochalski, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 135)
  #20050196
- Avalere Health / Carino, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 136)
  #20060211
- Medicare Rights Center / Hayes, 2005-2007 (Box 19, Folder 137)
  #20050310
- Medicare Rights Center / Hayes - Proposal Development, 2005-2007 (Box 19, Folder 138)
- Medicare Rights Center / Hayes - Grant Products, 2005-2007 (Box 20, Folder 139-140)
- Rutgers University / Reinhard, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 141-142)
  #20020439
- Research Triangle Institute / Trisolini, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 143)
  #20060506
- National Academy for State Health Policy / Rosenthal, 2007-2009 (Box 20, Folder 144)
  #20070765
- SHIRE / Perot, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 145)
  #200030678
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle, 2005-2007 (Box 21, Folder 146-147)
  #20050372
- American Society on Aging / Kleyman, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 148)
  #20070292
- Michigan State University / Nerenz, 1999-2003 (Box 21, Folder 149, Box 22, Folder 150-154, Box 23, Folder 155)
  #20000507
- Brigham and Women's Hospital / Johnson, 2000-2006 (Box 23, Folder 156)
  #20010109
- Brigham and Women's Hospital / Johnson - Proposal Development, 2000-2006 (Box 23, Folder 157)
- Brigham and Women's Hospital / Johnson - Grant Products, 2000-2006 (Box 23, Folder 158)
- Association of American Medical Colleges / Gamble, 2000-2005 (Box 23, Folder 159)
  #20010135
- Association of American Medical Colleges / Gamble - Proposal Development, 2000-2005 (Box 24, Folder 160)
- Association of American Medical Colleges / Gamble - Grant Products, 2000-2005 (Box 24, Folder 161-163)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine / Chassin, 2000-2007 (Box 24, Folder 164, Box 25, Folder 165)
  #20010102
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine / Chassin - Proposal Development, 2000-2007 (Box 25, Folder 166)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine / Chassin - Grant Products, 2000-2007 (Box 25, Folder 167)
- National Council on Interpreting Health Care / Roat, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 168, Box 26, Folder 169-171)
  #20030797
- Southwestern Medical Center / Flores, 2007-2009 (Box 26, Folder 171A, Box 27, Folder 172)
  #20070335
- Medical College of Wisconsin / Flores, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 173-176, Box 28, Folder 177)
  #20030335
- Medical College of Wisconsin / Flores, 2013.091.002-2013.91.003 (Box 27, Folder 173-176, Box 28, Folder 177)
  Conditions Governing Access
  No access copy available. Researchers interested in digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, please contact an archivist.
  Scope and Contents
  "Parents Helping Parents with Asthma"
- Massachusetts General Hospital / Weinick, 2006-2009 (Box 28, Folder 178-180)
  #20070081
- National Quality Forum / Burstin, 2007-2009 (Box 28, Folder 181-182, Box 29, Folder 183)
  #20070543
- George Washington University / Siegel, 2006-2008 (Box 29, Folder 184)
  #20070290
- National Quality Forum / Nishimi, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 185-186)
  #20030894
- Tufts - New England Medical Center / Perrin, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 187)
  #20080126
- University of South Florida / Simpson, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 188, Box 30, Folder 189-190)
  #20031137
- New York Academy of Medicine / Gray, 2003-2010 (Box 30, Folder 191)
  #20031259
- New York Academy of Medicine / Gray - Proposal Development, 2003-2010 (Box 30, Folder 192)
- New York Academy of Medicine / Gray - Grant Products, 2003-2010 (Box 30, Folder 193)
- Boston Medical Center / Smith, 2001-2007 (Box 30, Folder 194)
  #20020505
- Boston Medical Center / Smith - Articles and Background, 2001-2007 (Box 31, Folder 195)
- Boston Medical Center / Smith - Proposal Development, 2001-2007 (Box 31, Folder 196)
- Boston Medical Center / Smith - Grant Products, 2001-2007 (Box 31, Folder 197)
- New York University / Gany, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 198)
  #20020109
- New York University / Gany - Proposal Development, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 199)
- New York University / Gany - Grant Products, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 200, Box 32, Folder 201)
- The Regents of the University of California / Schillinger, 2001-2005 (Box 32, Folder 202)
  #20020122
- The Regents of the University of California / Schillinger, 2013.0913.004-2013.91.008 (Box 32, Folder 202)
  No access copy available. Researchers interested in accession digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, please contact an archivist.
  IDEALL Facilitator Training Disks 1-5
- The Regents of the University of California / Schillinger - Proposal Development, 2001-2005 (Box 32, Folder 203)
- The Regents of the University of California / Schillinger - Grant Products, 2001-2005 (Box 32, Folder 204-205, Box 33, Folder 206)
- New England Medical Center Hospitals / Safran, 2005-2007 (Box 33, Folder 207)
  #20060118
- New England Medical Center Hospitals / Safran - Proposal Development, 2005-2007 (Box 33, Folder 208-209)
- New England Medical Center Hospitals / Safran, 2005-2007 (Box 33, Folder 210)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle, 2007-2008 (Box 33, Folder 211)
  #20070790
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle - Proposal Development, 2007-2008 (Box 34, Folder 212)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance / Scholle - Grant Products, 2007-2008 (Box 34, Folder 213)
- Health Management Associates / Silow-Carroll, 2009-2010 (Box 34, Folder 214)
  #20100280
- Massachusetts Senior Care Foundation / Bonner, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 215)
  #20090266
- Pacific Business Group on Health / Fisher, 2006-2008 (Box 34, Folder 216)
  #20060612
- Pacific Business Group on Health / Fisher - Proposal Development, 2006-2008 (Box 34, Folder 217)
- Pacific Business Group on Health / Fisher - Grant Products, 2006-2008 (Box 35, Folder 218)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine / Keyhani, 2007-2008 (Box 35, Folder 219)
  #20070500
- AcademyHealth / Martinez-Vidal, 2007-2008 (Box 35, Folder 220)
  #20070766
- Center for Health Policy Development / Kaye, 2007-2009 (Box 35, Folder 221)
  #20070800
- Center for Health Policy Development / Kaye - Proposal Development, 2007-2009 (Box 35, Folder 222)
- Center for Health Policy Development / Kaye - Grant Products, 2007-2009 (Box 36, Folder 223-224)
- AcademyHealth / Davis, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 225)
  #20080413
- National Public Health and Hospital Institute / Cummings, 2007-2010 (Box 36, Folder 226)
  #20080031
- National Public Health and Hospital Institute / Cummings - Proposal Development, 2007-2010 (Box 36, Folder 227)
- International Society for Quality in Health Care / Tregloan, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 228)
  #20070827
- Massachusetts Health Data Consortium / Stone, 2000-2002 (Box 37, Folder 229-230)
  #20010138
- Johns Hopkins University / Gaskin, 2005-2008 (Box 37, Folder 231)
  #20060113
- Johns Hopkins University / Gaskin - Proposal Development, 2005-2008 (Box 37, Folder 232)
- Johns Hopkins University / Gaskin - Grant Products, 2005-2008 (Box 37, Folder 233)
- American Board of Internal Medicine Foundation / Gray, 2009-2011 (Box 37, Folder 234)
  #20090259
- Oregon Health and Sciences University / Reuland, 2007-2009 (Box 38, Folder 235)
  #20070793
- National Health Law Program / Youdelman, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 236)
  #20030737
- National Health Law Program / Youdelman - Proposal Development, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 237)
- National Health Law Program / Youdelman - Grant Products, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 238)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Health Care Organizations / Loeb, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 239-240)
  #20030862
- Center for Health Care Strategies / Bella, 2007-2011 (Box 39, Folder 241)
  #20070345
- Center for Health Care Strategies / Bella - Proposal Development (Box 39, Folder 242)
- National Health Law Program / Youdelman, 2002-20047 (Box 39, Folder 243-245)
  20030072
- Health Research and Educational Trust / Hasnain Wynia, 2002-2005 (Box 40, Folder 246)
  #20020739
- Health Research and Educational Trust / Hasnain-Wynia-Proposal Development, 2002-2005 (Box 40, Folder 247)
- Health Research and Educational Trust / Hasnain-Wynia - Grant Products, 2002-2005 (Box 40, Folder 248)
- American Medical Association Foundation / Wynia, 2004-2006 (Box 40, Folder 249-250)
  #20050019
- Association of Clinicians for the Underserved / Westpheling, 2005-2006 (Box 41, Folder 251-252)
  #20050400
- Wake Forest University Health Sciences / Woods, 2004-2006 (Box 41, Folder 253)
  #20040812
- Wake Forest University Health Sciences / Woods - Grant Products, 2004-2006 (Box 41, Folder 254-255)
- The Commonwealth Fund / Beal, 2005-2006 (Box 42, Folder 256-258)
  #20060021
- Drexel University / Andrulis, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 259)
  #20060338
- Health Research and Educational Trust / Wynia, 2005-2008 (Box 42, Folder 260)
  #20050475
- Medical College of Wisconsin / Flores, 2004-2007 (Box 43, Folder 261)
  #20050068
- National Academy of Sciences / Behmey, 2006-2008 (Box 43, Folder 262-263)
  #20070140
- WGBH Educational Foundation / Kaplan, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 264)
  #20031339
- WGBH Educational Foundation / Kaplan, 2013.091.009-2013.091.012 (Box 43, Folder 264)
  "Retooling for an Aging America: Highlight Reel" "Retooling for an Aging America: Building the Health Care Workforce" "From the WGBH Health Desk for Markpetplace - Story Samples"
- New York University / Gany, 2004-2007 (Box 44, Folder 265)
  #20040414
- New York University / Gany - Proposal Development, 2004-2007 (Box 44, Folder 266)
- New York University / Gany - Grant Products, 2004-2007 (Box 44, Folder 267)
- The Regents of the University of California / Schillinger, 2004-2006 (Box 44, Folder 268)
  #20040677
- The Regents of the University of California / Schillinger - Proposal Development, 2004-2006 (Box 44, Folder 269)
- The Regents of the University of California / Schillinger - Grant Products, 2004-2006 (Box 45, Folder 270)
- Health Research and Educational Trust / Wynia, 2004-2006 (Box 45, Folder 271)
  #20040675
- Health Research and Educational Trust / Wynia - Proposal Development, 2004-2006 (Box 45, Folder 274)
- Health Research and Educational Trust / Wynia - Grant Products, 2004-2006 (Box 44, Folder 273)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College / Hsiao, 2011-2012 (Box 45, Folder 274)
  #20110109